dermnet.com 2011-11-23

# Dermnet: Dermatology Pictures - Skin Disease Pictures

## Privacy Statement

Last Update August 2010

## Introduction

Interactive Medical Media is committed to protecting your privacy. This statement details the steps we take to protect your personal information when you visit our websites. It describes the personal information that we collect, the purposes for which we use such information, and your choices regarding our use of it. The steps we take to protect your personal information and how you can review and correct your personal information are also covered here. By accessing our websites, you are consenting to the information collection and use practices described in this privacy statement.

## Our collection of information

Information collected directly from you. Generally, you can visit Interactive Medical Media's websites without entering any personal information. On certain pages, we may ask you for personal information to provide a service or carry out a transaction that you have requested. The personal information we collect may include:

  * contact details, such as your name, company/organization name, e-mail address, telephone and fax numbers, and physical address;
  * information about your company, and job function;
  * your e-mail marketing preferences;
  * financial information (including credit card or account information);
  * information used to customize and facilitate your use of our websites, including login and technical information;
  * inquiries about and orders for our products and services;
  * information that assists us in identifying the products and services that best meet your requirements;
  * feedback from you about our websites and our products and services generally.

You are not required to provide any of this information, but if you do not, we may not be able to provide you the requested service or complete your transaction.

## Information collected automatically 

We collect information about your visit to our sites, including what pages you view, the number of bytes transferred, the links you click, the materials you access, and other actions taken within Interactive Medical Media's sites. On sites that you enter with a user ID, we may connect this information with your identity to determine your potential interests in our products and services. We also collect certain standard information that your browser sends to every website you visit, such as your Internet Protocol (IP) address, your browser type and capabilities and language, your operating system, the date and time you access the site, and the website from which you linked to our site. We do not link this information to your identity.

## Our use of information

Services and transactions. We use your personal information to deliver services or carry out transactions you have requested, such as providing information on Interactive 

Medical Media products, registering purchased products, processing product orders, answering customer service requests, facilitating use of our websites, and so forth. In order to offer you a more consistent experience in your interactions with Interactive Medical Media, information collected by our websites may be combined with information we collect by other means.

Website improvement.  We may use your personal information to improve our websites and related Interactive Medical Media products or services, or to make our websites easier to use by eliminating the need for you to repeatedly enter the same information or by customizing our websites to your particular preference or interests.   
Communications. With your permission, we may use your personal information gathered via our websites to inform you of products or services available from Interactive Medical Media. When collecting information that might be used to contact you about our products and services, we will always give you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving such communications. Moreover, each e-mail communication we send includes an unsubscribe link allowing you to stop delivery of that type of communication. If you elect to unsubscribe, we will remove you from the relevant list within 10 business days.

Our use of cookies and web beacons  
Cookies are small files that websites save to your hard disk or to your browser's memory. We may use them to track the number of times you have visited the site, to track the number of visitors to the site, to determine and analyze visitors' use of our sites (including the effectiveness of online advertising), to store information that you provide such as your preferences, and to store technical information useful for your interactions with our websites. We may use session cookies (cookies that are deleted when your browser session ends) to store your user ID, elements of your user profile, to facilitate your movement around our websites (particularly in connection with information searches and order placement) and other information useful in administering the session. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser settings to decline cookies or to notify you when a cookie is being placed on your computer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the features of Interactive Medical Media's websites or other websites that you visit. Our sites also may contain electronic images known as web beacons - sometimes called single-pixel gifs - that allow us to count the number of users who have visited those pages. We may include web beacons in promotional e-mail messages or Newsletters in order to determine whether messages have been opened and acted upon. 

## Disclosure of your personal information

Except as described below, personal information you provide to Interactive Medical Media through our websites will not be shared outside of Interactive Medical Media and its controlled subsidiaries and affiliates without your permission.

Disclosure to service providers. Interactive Medical Media contracts with other companies to provide services on our behalf, such as hosting websites, sending out information, processing transactions, and analyzing our websites. We provide these companies with only those elements of your personal information they need to deliver those services. These companies and their employees are prohibited from using that personal information for any other purpose. 

Disclosure to distributors. In responding to a request made by you, we may share your personal information with companies that distribute our products. In those cases, we provide these companies with only those elements of your personal information they need to respond to your request, and these companies and their employees are prohibited from using that personal information for any other purpose. In some cases, we may seek your permission to share your information with distributors for marketing purposes other than responding to a request from you. However, we will not share your information for such marketing purposes unless we have obtained your express consent to do so.

Disclosure in connection with transactions. In connection with certain transactions, we may disclose some or all of your personal information to financial institutions, government entities, and shipping companies or postal services involved in fulfillment.

Disclosures in connection with acquisitions or divestitures. Circumstances may arise where for strategic or other business reasons Interactive Medical Media decides to sell, buy, merge or otherwise reorganize businesses in some countries. Such a transaction may involve the disclosure of personal information to prospective or actual purchasers, or receiving it from sellers. It is Interactive Medical Media's practice to seek appropriate protection for information in these types of transactions.

Disclosure for other reasons. We may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with legal requirements or with legal process served on us, to protect and defend our rights or property, or in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of any individual. 

## Security

Interactive Medical Media is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. For example, we store the personal information you provide on computer systems with limited access that are located in facilities to which access is limited. For sites to which you login, it is your responsibility to ensure the security of your password and not to reveal this information to others. When you move around a site to which you have logged in, or from one site to another that uses the same login mechanism, we verify your identity by means of an encrypted cookie placed on your machine.

## Reviewing your personal information

In some cases, you can review and correct personal information provided through our websites by going to the page on which you provided the information. In all cases, you can make a request to review and correct your personal information collected via our websites or ask Interactive Medical Media to stop using it by completing our Contact Us form. We may take steps to verify your identity before providing you access to your personal information. You can help us to maintain the accuracy of your information by notifying us of any change to your phone number, or e-mail address. 

## Consent to international transfers of personal information

The personal information we collect on our websites may be sent to the United States or to any other country in which Interactive Medical Media or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities. We may also store and process the information there. Although the laws that protect personal information in those countries may differ from the laws where you live, we will take reasonable steps to ensure that your privacy is protected. By using our websites and giving your information to us, you consent to the transfer of the data outside of your country. 

## Children's information

Interactive Medical Media does not knowingly collect information from children and does not target or direct its websites to children.

## Links to other sites

Our websites may contain links to other sites such as Interactive Medical Media distributors and sales affiliates, professional and government organizations, and publications. We also link to third-party providers that host, maintain and operate on-line training curricula. While we try to link only to sites that share our high standards and respect for privacy, we are not responsible for the content, security, or privacy practices employed by other sites.

## Enforcement of this privacy statement

If you have questions regarding this statement or our handling of your personal information, please Contact Us. We will promptly address your concern and strive to reach a satisfactory resolution. 

## Changes to this privacy statement

Interactive Medical Media may occasionally update this privacy statement. When we do, we will revise the "last updated" date at the top of the privacy statement. We will obtain your opt-in consent for any updates to this privacy statement that materially expand the sharing or use of your personal information in ways not disclosed in this privacy statement at the time of collection.
